A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Jobs, 1
  - 763b - New Directions in Community Revitalization, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 706)
  - 763c - Uptown Gardens, Denver, Colorado, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 707)
  - 764 - Benito Rubino Center for the Defense of Human Rights, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 708)
  - 765 - Grupo de Assessaria Juridica as Organizacoes Populares, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 709)
  - 766 - SOS CORPO Women's Center of Cabo, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 710)
  - 767 - Luis Freire Cultural Center, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 711)
  - 768 - Videomaker Adauto de Souza, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 712)
  - 769 - Professional Association of Domestic Employees, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 713)
  - 770 - Sao Martinho Beneficent Association, 1989 October (Box 46, Folder 714)
  - 771 - FF Leadership for Community Foundations, 1989 February (Box 46, Folder 715)
  - 772 - Race Relations and Campus Diversity, 1990 May (Box 46, Folder 716)
    Photographer: Simmons, Howard E.
  - 773 - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture, 1990 April (Box 46, Folder 717)
    Photographer: Hausbrandt, Jan
    Poland
  - 774 - El Paso Community Foundation, 1990 April (Box 46, Folder 718)
    Photographer: Taylor, Isabele Fierro
  - 775 - Education and Culture ?Judith Eaton? American Council on Education, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 719)
  - 776 - Gladys Thatcher San Francisco Education Fund, 1990 February (Box 47, Folder 720)
  - 777 - Rural Poverty: Susan Seckler and Mil Duncan of Aspen Institute, 1990 March (Box 47, Folder 721)
  - 778 - Dr. Thomas Cole, President, Clark Atlanta University, 1990 February (Box 47, Folder 722)
    Photographer: Nelson, Rob
  - 780 - Innovating America Wetlands, Arcata, CA, 1989 November (Box 47, Folder 723)
  - 781 - Innovations: Shaker Heights, Cleveland, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 724)
    Photographer: Century, Janet
  - 782 - Innovations: C.A.R.E. Program, 1989 November (Box 47, Folder 725)
    Photographer: Bohn, Gary
  - 783 - Innovations: STEP St. Paul, 1990 October (Box 47, Folder 726)
    Photographer: Wait, Steve
  - 784 - Innovations: One Church, One Child, 1990 April (Box 47, Folder 727)
    Photographer: Pokempner, Mark
  - 785 - Innovations: Family Learning Center, 1989 October (Box 47, Folder 728)
    Photographer: Crisostomo, Manny
  - 786 - Innovations: Parents as Teachers, St. Louis, MO, 1989 October (Box 47, Folder 729)
  - 787 - Innovations: Alternatives to Incarceration, Atlanta, 1989 November (Box 47, Folder 730, Box 134, Folder 1954)
  - 788 - Innovations 1990: Inupiat Ilitqusiat: Traditional Values, Alaska (Box 48, Folder 731)
  - 789 - Innovations 1990: Specialized Treatment and Rehabilitation Services for Sexually Abused Boys (STARS) program (Box 48, Folder 732)
  - 790 - Innovations 1990: Landfill Reclamation Project (Box 48, Folder 733)
  - 791 - Innovations 1990: Farm Family Assistance Program (Box 48, Folder 734)
  - 792 - Innovations 1990: Project Deliver - Quality Obstetrical Care, Rockville, Maryland (Box 48, Folder 735)
  - 793 - Innovations 1990: Work Force Unemployment Prevention Program (Box 48, Folder 736)
  - 794 - Innovations 1990: Electronic Benefit System (Box 48, Folder 737)
  - 795 - Innovations 1990: XPORT, Port Authority Trading Company (Box 48, Folder 738)
  - 796 - Innovations 1990: Medical Care for Children Project (Box 49, Folder 739)
  - 797 - Innovations 1990: Seattle Recycling Project (Box 49, Folder 740)
  - 798 - California Resource and Referral Network, 1990 June (Box 49, Folder 741)
  - 799 - Neighborhood Child Care Network, 1990 June (Box 49, Folder 742)
  - 800 - Coastal Enterprises, Inc., 1990 June (Box 49, Folder 743)
    Photographer: Abramson, Dean
  - 801 - Energy Conservation and Facilities Management Corp., 1990 June (Box 49, Folder 744)
    Photographer: Staller, Jan
  - 802 - Jose Barzelatto - portraits, 1990 June (Box 49, Folder 745)
    Photographer: Bogdan, Gary
  - 803 - THE DOOR, 121 Ave of the Americas, New York, NY (Ford Foundation Letter, January 1991), 1990 November (Box 49, Folder 746)
    Photographer: Rosenthal, Mel
  - 804 - Water Supply Foundation, Poland, 1991 February (Box 49, Folder 747)
  - 805a - Innovations 1990: Inupiat Ilitqusiat: Traditional Values, Alaska (captions) (Box 49, Folder 748)
  - 805b - Innovations 1990: Specialized Treatment and Rehabilitation Services for Sexually Abused Boys (STARS) program (captions) (Box 50, Folder 749)
  - 805c - Innovations 1990: Landfill Reclamation Project (captions) (Box 51, Folder 750)
  - 805d - Innovations 1990: Farm Family Assistance Program (captions) (Box 52, Folder 751)
  - 805e - Innovations 1990: Project Deliver - Quality Obstetrical Care, Rockville, Maryland (captions) (Box 53, Folder 752)
  - 805f - Innovations 1990: Work Force Unemployment Prevention Program (captions) (Box 54, Folder 753)
  - 805g - Innovations 1990: Electronic Benefit System (captions) (Box 55, Folder 754)
  - 805h - Innovations 1990: Seattle Recycling Project (captions) (Box 56, Folder 755)
  - 805i - Innovations 1990: Medical Care for Children Project (captions) (Box 57, Folder 756)
  - 805j - Innovations 1990: XPORT, Port Authority Trading Company (captions) (Box 58, Folder 757)
  - 806 - Innovations 1990: The Film Forum, New York (Box 49, Folder 758)
  - 807 - University of North Carolina (Life Journeys of Women in Corps), 1990 September (Box 49, Folder 759)
  - 808 - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1990 December (Box 49, Folder 760)
    Photographer: Bishop, G. Thomas
  - 809 - University of Maryland (School of Public Affairs), 1991 January (Box 49, Folder 761)
    Photographer: Bloom, Richard A.
  - 810 - University of Pittsburgh QUASAR, Iris Carl, Houston, 1991 January (Box 49, Folder 762)
    Photographer: Rubin, Janice
  - 811 - National Council of Less Commonly Taught Languages, 1991 January (Box 50, Folder 763)
  - 812 - Women's Program Forum Conference at Ford Foundation, 1991 February (Box 50, Folder 764)
  - 813 - 1990 Community Foundation Leadership Awards, 1991 January (Box 50, Folder 765)
  - 814 - Youth Build (Boston), 1990 November (Box 50, Folder 766)
    Photographer: Johnson, Stella
  - 815 - Johnson C. Smith University, 1990 November (Box 50, Folder 767)
    Photographer: Pierce, Nancy
  - 816 - Tacolcy Economic Development Corp., 1990 November (Box 50, Folder 768)
    Photographer: Willens, Kathy
  - 817 - Dr. Margaret Spencer (Emory University, Atlanta), 1990 November (Box 50, Folder 769)
  - 818 - European Cooperation Fund/East-West Parliamentary Practice Project, 1991 January (Box 50, Folder 770)
  - 819 - Mexican American Museum, San Francisco, CA, 1991 April (Box 50, Folder 771)
  - 820 - Studio Museum in Harlem, New York, 1991 April (Box 50, Folder 772)
  - 821 - Institute of Bio-Social Research and Development, India, 1991 April (Box 50, Folder 773, 774, 775)
    Photographer: Bartholomew, Pablo
  - 823 - Ford Foundation Overseas Administrators, Ford Foundation Headquarters, New York, 1991 May (Box 50, Folder 776)
  - 824 - Eyes on the Prize (Fall 1991 'Ford Foundation Letter'), 1991 May (Box 50, Folder 777)
  - 825 - Franklin Thomas at the Minnesota Meeting, 1991 October (Box 50, Folder 778)
    Photographer: Peterson, Brian
  - 826 - Human Rights in South Africa, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 779)
    Photographer: Kauffman, Sam
    South Africa
  - 827a - Neighborhood Housing Services of America (Oakland, CA) (Box 51, Folder 780)
    Photographer: Pokempner, Mark; Immanuel Manor
  - 827b - Appalshop - Program Related Investment (PRI), 1991 (Box 51, Folder 781)
  - 827c - YWCA of Jersey City, 1991 August (Box 51, Folder 782)
  - 827d - Tacolcy Economic Development Corp. Miami, FL, 1991 September (Box 51, Folder 783)
  - 827e - The Research Libraries Group Inc., 1991 September (Box 51, Folder 784)
    Photographer: Maynard, Chris
  - 827f - The Studio Museum in Harlem, 1991 August (Box 51, Folder 785)
  - 827g - Public Interest Law Center (PILC) New York, NY, 1991 August (Box 51, Folder 786)
  - 827h - Mountain Association for Community Economic Development (MACED), 1991 August (Box 51, Folder 787)
    Photographer: Brunner Studios
  - 828a - Innovations 1991, John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1991 July (Box 51, Folder 788)
    Photographer: Reed, Eli
  - 828b - Innovations 1991, K-Sex Early Intervention Partnership (Box 51, Folder 789)
  - 828c - Innovations 1991, Trauma Intervention Program (TIP) (Box 51, Folder 790)
  - 828d - Innovations 1991, Georgia No-Tillage Assistance Program (Box 51, Folder 791)
  - 828e - Innovations 1991, KET Star Channels, Commonwealth of Kentucky (Box 51, Folder 792)
  - 828f - Innovations 1991, Friends of the Family (Box 51, Folder 793)
  - 828g - Innovations 1991, The Blackstone Project: Preventing Pollution Before it Starts (Box 52, Folder 794)
  - 828h - Innovations 1991, School-based Youth Services (Box 52, Folder 795)
  - 828i - Innovations 1991, Philadelphia Anti-Graffiti Network (Box 52, Folder 796)
  - 828j - Innovations 1991, Monroe Maternity Center (Box 52, Folder 797)
  - 828k - Innovations 1991, Seattle Neighborhood Matching Fund (Box 52, Folder 798)
  - 828l - Innovations 1991, Slide Show (Box 52, Folder 799)
  - 829 - Native American Rights Fund: Tribal Court in Concho, Oklahoma, 1991 October (Box 52, Folder 800)
    Photographer: Hellstern, Paul
  - 830 - Native American Rights Fund: Rosebud Reservation, South Dakota, 1991 October (Box 52, Folder 801)
    Photographer: Lindblade, G.R.
  - 831 - Youth Build, Boston, MA, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 802)
  - 832 - Zimbabwe, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 803, 804)
    Photographer: Watson, Carolyn
  - 833 - Mozambique, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 805)
    Mozambique
  - 834 - Community Development Corps., 1991 November (Box 53, Folder 806)
  - 835 - Bishop Desmond Tutu, 1992 January (Box 53, Folder 807)
  - 836 - Nelson Mandela (unofficial visit to Ford Foundation), 1991 December (Box 53, Folder 808)
  - 837 - Crossroads Theater Company, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 809)
    Photographer: Peters, Mike
  - 838 - Women and the Media, 1992 May (Box 53, Folder 810)
    Photographer: Ianuzzi, Tom
  - 839 - Racism in Brazil, 1992 April (Box 53, Folder 811)
    Photographer: Posner, Andrew
  - 840 - Legal Status of Women in Latin America, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 812)
    Photographer: Stein, Avani
  - 841 - Youth Commission, N. Carolina, 1992 August (Box 53, Folder 813)
    Photographer: Strickland, Jim
  - 842a - Innovations 1992: Automated Traffic Surveillance and Control (Box 54, Folder 814)
    Photographer: Butow, David
  - 842b - Humanitas (Innovations 1992) (Box 54, Folder 815)
  - 842c - Innovations 1992: Environmental Clean-Up Project (Box 54, Folder 816)
    Photographer: Johnson, Lynn
  - 842d - Innovations 1992: City Works (Box 54, Folder 817)
  - 842e - Innovations 1992: Quincy Court (Box 54, Folder 818)
  - 842f - Innovations 1992: New York City Sanitarium (Box 54, Folder 819)
    Photographer: Wells, David
  - 842g - Innovations 1992: CAP Child Assistance Program (Box 54, Folder 820)
  - 842h - Innovations 1992: Bilingual Outreach (Box 54, Folder 821)
  - 842i - Innovations 1992: Elderly Services (Box 54, Folder 822)
  - 842j - Innovations 1992: Workers Compensation (Box 54, Folder 823)
  - 843 - Fathers and Families: Childrens Network, 1992 June (Box 54, Folder 824)
    Photographer: Kostans, Eleftherios
  - 844 - Working Capital, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 825)
  - 848 - Women's Program Forum, 1992 May (Box 54, Folder 826)
  - 849 - University of Massachusetts - Boston Diversity Program, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 827)
  - 850 - China: Angwan Village, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 828, Box 134, Folder 1955)
    Photographer: Orick, George
  - 851 - Mount St. Mary's College: Winter, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 829)
  - 852 - Princeton University Seminar, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 830)
  - 853 - Woman's Studies Program Forum Seminar at Ford Foundation, 1992 November (Box 54, Folder 831)
    Photographer: Vaughan, Garth
  - 854a - QUASAR: Portsmouth Middle School, Portland, Oregon, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 832)
    Photographer: Johnson, Shelah
  - 854b - QUASAR, Milwaukee: Edison Middle School: Education and Culture, 1993 May (Box 55, Folder 833)
    Photographer: Schneff, James
  - 854c - QUASAR, Pittsburgh: Ed Silver, 1993 June (Box 55, Folder 834)
    Photographer: Goldsmith, Scott
  - 854d - QUASAR, Portland, Oregon: Portsmouth Middle School: Education and Culture, 1993 June (Box 55, Folder 835)
    Photographer: Finnegan, Kristin
  - 854e - QUASAR, Milwaukee: Edison Middle School: Education and Culture, 1993 June (Box 55, Folder 836)
    Photographer: Corsmeier, Christ
  - 855 - New York Theological Seminary Graduate Students: Annual Report, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 837)
    Photographer: Siegal, Ken
  - 856 - National Women?s Law Center, Annual Report, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 838)
  - 857 - Public Interest Law Center (PILC), 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 839)
    Photographer: Friedman, Benno
  - 858 - Pittsburgh Partnership for Neighborhood Development - PRI, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 840)
    Photographer: Aschkenas, David
  - 859 - Radio Bilingue (Fresno, California) Rights and Social Justice program, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 841)
    Photographer: Zamora, Eric Paul
  - 860 - University Settlement House, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 842)
    Photographer: Goldman, Marion
  - 861 - NALEO Citizen Workshop, 1993 January (Box 55, Folder 843)
    Photographer: Suma, Ann
  - 862 - Ford Foundation Youth Commission Touring Boston, 1992 August (Box 55, Folder 844)
  - 863 - In the Mix, 1992 October (Box 55, Folder 845)
    Photographer: Weiner, Walter; Wren, K. Reene
  - 864 - Preserving Indonesian Manuscript, 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 846)
  - 865 - Malcolm X Documentary (Blackside Productions), 1993 March (Box 55, Folder 847)
  - 866 - Malcolm X Documentary (Allison Windom Interview), 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 848)
    Photographer: Van Horn, James T.
  - 867 - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 849)
    Photographer: McSpadden, Wyatt
  - 868 - West African Museum Project, 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 850)
    Africa
  - 869 - Wider Opportunities for Women, 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 851)
    Photographer: Coleman, Elizabeth
  - 870 - Wider Opportunities for Women (WOW), Montana, 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 852)
    Photographer: Brewster, Will
  - 871 - Wider Opportunities for Women (Wisconsin), 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 853)
    Photographer: Miller, Buck
  - 872 - Conference in Equity and Educational Testing, 1993 March (Box 56, Folder 854)
  - 873 - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG), 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 855)
    Photographer: Ruiz, Elsa
  - 874 - U.S. Committee on Legal Education Exchanges with China, 1993 July (Box 56, Folder 856)
  - 875 - Professor Naff at the University of Pennsylvania, 1992 November (Box 56, Folder 857)
    Photographer: Skoogfors, Leif
  - 876 - Memorial, Human Rights Project (Moscow), 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 858)
    Photographer: Binder, Ellen
    Russia
  - 877 - Moscow, Russia, 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 859)
  - 878 - Democracy After Communism (DAC), Hungary, 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 860)
    Photographer: Chris Niedenthal.
  - 879 - Stefan Batory Foundation, Poland (International Affairs program), 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 861)
  - 880 - SOS, Social Assistance Foundation, Warsaw, Poland (International Affairs program), 1993 May (Box 56, Folder 862, Box 134, Folder 1956)
    Photographer: Jan Hausbrandt.
  - 881 - Employment Center, Moscow, Russia (International Affairs program), 1993 June (Box 56, Folder 863)
    Photographer: Swersy, Bill
  - 882 - Ford Foundation Summer Interns, 1993 August (Box 56, Folder 864)
    Photographer: John T. Miller
  - 883 - Center for Housing and Urban Studies, Mexico, 1993 June (Box 57, Folder 865)
    Photographer: Stella Johnson.
  - 884 - Alternatives and Social Participation Processes, Mexico, 1993 June (Box 57, Folder 866)
  - 885 - Comprehensive Health for Women, Mexico, 1993 June (Box 57, Folder 867)
  - 886 - Memorial, Russia, 1993 June (Box 57, Folder 868)
  - 887 - Cooperative Home Care Center, Bronx, New York, 1993 September (Box 57, Folder 869)
    Photographer: Alex Forman
  - 888 - Citywide Coalition, Seattle Schools, Seattle, Washington, 1993 April (Box 57, Folder 870, 871)
    Photographer: Robert Lyons
  - 889a - Innovations 1993: INFO / California, State of California, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 872)
  - 889b - Innovations 1993: Telecommuting, County of Los Angeles, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 873)
  - 889c - Innovations 1993: Computer Centers, City of Lansing, Michigan, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 874)
  - 889d - Innovations 1993: Central Park East, New York City Board of Education, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 875)
  - 889e - Innovations 1993: Urban Land Project, Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 876)
  - 889f - Innovations 1993: Vendor Information program, State of Oregon, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 877)
  - 889g - Innovations 1993: Police Homeowners Loan, City of Columbia, South Carolina, 1993 August (Box 57, Folder 878)
  - 889h - Innovations 1993: Child Care Management, State of Texas, 1993 August (Box 58, Folder 879)
  - 889i - Innovations 1993: Voicemail for the Phoneless, City of Seattle, Washington, 1993 August (Box 58, Folder 880)
  - 889j - Innovations 1993: Low Income Mortgage, State of West Virginia, 1993 August (Box 58, Folder 881)
  - 890 - Women in South Africa, 1993 July (Box 58, Folder 882)
    Photographer: Roger Bosch
  - 891 - Women in South Africa, 1993 July (Box 58, Folder 883)
    Photographer: Louise Gubb
  - 892 - National Women's Coalition / University of Witwatersrand, 1993 July (Box 58, Folder 884)
  - 893 - Women's Program Forum, Women and Agriculture in Africa, 1993 November (Box 58, Folder 885)
    Photographer: Stephanie Hollyman
  - 894 - National Coalition of AIDS Partnership, Newark, New Jersey, 1993 November (Box 58, Folder 886)
    Photographer: Stephen Shames. Spring 1994 FF ?Report?.
  - 895 - National Coalition of AIDS Partnership, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1993 November (Box 58, Folder 887)
    Photographer: Rob Amberg. Spring 1994 FF ?Report?.
  - 896 - Community Foundations Meeting in San Francisco, 1993 November (Box 58, Folder 888)
    Photographer: Fred Mertz. 1993 FF Annual Report.
  - 897 - MALDEF Leadership Training Workshop, 1993 December (Box 58, Folder 889)
    Photographer: Steven Smith. Winter 1993 FF 'Report'.
  - 898 - American Social History Project, 1993 December (Box 58, Folder 890)
    Photographer: Stephanie Hollyman. Winter 1993 FF 'Report'.
  - 899 - NEICORP Upper Peninsula, Michigan, 1993 December (Box 58, Folder 891)
    Photographer: Kevin Horan. Winter 1993 FF 'Report'.
  - 900 - Inspiration Caf for Youth Commission Report, 1993 August (Box 58, Folder 892)
    Photographer: Kevin Horan.
  - 901 - Economist Richard Freeman, 1994 April (Box 58, Folder 893)
  - 902 - Authors of 'Building Bridges', 1994 March (Box 58, Folder 894)
    Photographer: Richard Bloom.
  - 903 - Street Vendors of Minia, Egypt, 1993 November (Box 58, Folder 895)
    Photographer: Deborah Pugh.
  - 904 - Food Vendor in Cairo, Egypt, 1994; April (Box 59, Folder 896)
    Photographer: Sean Sprague.
  - 905 - Scholars from the University of Toronto, 1994 January (Box 59, Folder 897)
    Photographer David Hartman.
    Canada
  - 906 - Taos Community Economic Development Corporation, 1994 January (Box 59, Folder 898)
    Photographer: Adolphe Pierre-Louis.
  - 907 - Piton Foundation -Black Churches, 1994 January (Box 59, Folder 899)
    Photographer: Barry Staver.
  - 908 - Law Firm of Steptoe and Johnson, 1994 January (Box 59, Folder 900)
  - 909 - African Housing Fund, Nairobi, Kenya, 1994 January (Box 59, Folder 901)
    Photographer: Fiona McDougall.
  - 910 - Northern Lights-Tam. Troubled Waters, Montana, 1992 October (Box 59, Folder 902)
    Photographer Laurance Aiuppy.
  - 911 - Thailand: A Model, 1994 March (Box 59, Folder 903)
    Photographer: Leah Melnick. Spring 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 912 - Women in the Military, 1994 June (Box 59, Folder 904)
  - 913 - Nigeria HIV/AIDS, 1994 June (Box 59, Folder 905)
    Photographer Slim Akeh. Summer 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 914 - Turning on the Power, 1994 June (Box 59, Folder 906)
    Photographer: Stephanie Hollyman. Summer 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 915 - Martin Marty, University of Chicago, 1994 June (Box 59, Folder 907)
    Photographer: Ilene Ehrlich. Summer 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 916 - Binmaley Nutrition, Food, Environment and Medicare program, Philippines, 1994 September (Box 59, Folder 908)
    Photographer: Edwin Tuyay.
  - 917 - Legal Research and Resource Center, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 909)
  - 918 - SABREEN Music Institute, Jerusalem, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 910)
  - 919 - Food Vendors, Cairo, Egypt, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 911)
  - 920 - Union of Palestinian Medical Relief, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 912)
    Palestine
  - 921 - Brazil - Unmasking an Epidemic, AIBA-Pela Vida HIV/AIDS outreach workers, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 913)
    Photographer: Vera Sayao.
  - 922 - Women / NAFTA, Mexico, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 914)
    Photographer: Graciela Iturbide.
  - 923 - Cairo, Egypt, Population Conference, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 915)
    Photographer: Mohamed Khaled Gouley. Fall 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 924a - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Quickcourt, Arizona (Box 60, Folder 916)
    Photographer: Current/Rutledge.
  - 924b - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Coles Levee Ecosystem Preserve, California (Box 60, Folder 917)
  - 924c - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Student Conflict Resolution (SCORE), Massachusetts (Box 60, Folder 918)
  - 924d - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Voluntary investigation and Cleanup, Minnesota (Box 60, Folder 919)
  - 924e - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Minnesota Parents' Fair Share (Box 60, Folder 920)
  - 924f - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Here, Thayer and Everywhere (Box 60, Folder 921)
  - 924g - Innovations 1994 Awardee: New York State Partnership for Long-Term Care (Box 60, Folder 922)
  - 924h - Innovations 1994 Awardee: New York Citywide Central Insurance (Box 60, Folder 923)
  - 924i - Innovations 1994 Awardee: SANE - OK (Box 60, Folder 924)
  - 924j - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Oregon Benchmarks (Box 60, Folder 925)
  - 925 - Innovations 1994 Awardee: Bill Treanor - Youth Today (Box 60, Folder 926)
    Photographer: Richard Bloom. Fall 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 926 - Coalition for Temporary Shelter, Detroit, Michigan, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 927)
    Photographer: Jim West, Impact Visuals
  - 927 - NAFTA and Mexico, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 928)
    Photographer: Jeffery Scott
  - 928 - Women's Study Group "Rosario Castellanos", Oaxaca, Mexico, 1994 December (Box 61, Folder 929)
  - 929 - Southern Regional Council, Ellis Turnage at courthouse in Atlanta, Georgia, 1994 December (Box 61, Folder 930)
    Photographer: Bill Moses.
  - 930 - Sunflower Elementary School, Sunflower MS, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 931)
    Photographer: David Rae Morris. Winter 1995 FF 'Report', Southern Regional Council article.
  - 931 - Tim Schmitz for EcoTrust Story, 1994 December (Box 61, Folder 932)
    Photographer: Rex Ziak. Winter 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 932 - New Community Corporation - Building Bridges, 1994 November (Box 61, Folder 933)
    Photographer: Jeanette Beckman
  - 933 - African Universities, 1994 November (Box 61, Folder 934)
    Photographer: Slim Akeh. Fall 1994 FF 'Report'.
  - 934 - Elaine Jones, NAACP Legal Defense Fund, 1994 Winter (Box 61, Folder 935)
  - 935 - WOW, Non-traditional employment training (NET) for women, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 936)
    Photographer: Stephen Shames. 1994 Annual Report, Urban Poverty program.
  - 936 - Urban Poverty program, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 937)
    Photographer: Stephen Shames. 1994 Annual Report shoot, various grantees.
  - 937 - African Universities - University of Ghana, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 938)